<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Images on Linux VM Images - Download VirtualBox and VMware Images</title>
    <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Images on Linux VM Images - Download VirtualBox and VMware Images</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 12:59:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 VM Images | Xubuntu 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Xubuntu 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Xubuntu 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish) features the beautiful Xfce desktop environment. Xubuntu 22.04 was released April 21, 2022 and will be supported for three years, until 2025.
Xubuntu 22.04 comes with Xfce 4.16, Mousepad 0.5.8, Ristretto 0.12.2, Whisker Menu Plugin 2.7.1 and Six new community wallpaper.
Read: New Features Of Xubuntu 22.04.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux 2022.1 VM Images | Kali Linux 2022.1 VirtualBox Image | Kali Linux 2022.1 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2022/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kali Linux 2022.1 is the first Kali Linux release for the year 2022. It comes with visual updates that includes new wallpapers for desktop, login, and boot displays, and a new theme.
This release also includes new tools such as dnsx, email2phonenumber, naabu, and many more.
You can read more about Kali Linux 2022.1 in release notes
You can also download pre-installed virtual images from the official site as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XeroLinux VM Images | XeroLinux VirtualBox Image | XeroLinux VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xerolinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xerolinux/</guid>
      <description>Introduction XeroLinux is a Linux distribution based on Arch Linux that comes with KDE Plasma Desktop. It is a personal project by DarkXero.
XeroLinux comes in 2 flavors, &amp;ldquo;Main Edition&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;XFCE Edition&amp;rdquo;.
The Main edition is the standard version with KDE as its desktop environment with lots of customization options, a variety of packages, supports for the vast number of the hardware.
The XFCE edition is a lightweight edition with XFCE as its desktop environment for people who do not have powerful hardware to run the Main edition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop!_OS 21.10 VM Images | Pop!_OS 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Pop!_OS 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pop!_OS 21.10 is the latest release from System76, Inc. It features the 5.15.5 kernel and the latest NVIDIA driver that supports a wide variety of hardware.
It includes Intuitive Refresh OS Feature, which helps in reinstalling the operating system without deleting the files in the Home folder.
Read Release Notes of Pop!_OS 21.10.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zorin OS 16 VM Images | Zorin OS 16 VirtualBox Image | Zorin OS 16 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/zorinos-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/zorinos-16/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Zorin OS is an open-source Linux distribution based on Ubuntu operating system. Zorin offers Zorin OS 16 Pro, Core, and Lite editions.
Zorin OS 16 is the most advanced version ever released by Zorin Group and is packed with lots of features and improvements. In addition, it comes with a more polished default theme where you will find detailed and delightful animations that will be pleasant for your eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepin 20.3 VM Images | Deepin 20.3 VirtualBox Image | Deepin 20.3 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-203/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Deepin is an open-source Linux distribution based on Debian&amp;rsquo;s stable branch. It features Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE), built on Qt and available for various distributions like Manjaro, Arch or Fedora.
Deepin 20.3 comes with a new kernel 5.15 (stable) with better support for Intel 12th Gen processors and NTFS file systems. You can read more about the new release in the release notes.
Here, we provide ready to use Deepin 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Linux 8.5 VM Images | Rocky Linux 8.5 VirtualBox Image | Rocky Linux 8.5 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/rockylinux-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/rockylinux-8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Rocky Linux is a community enterprise operating system designed to be 100% compatible with Red Hat Enterprise Linux.
It is a completely free OS and developed by the community led by Gregory Kurtzer, founder of the CentOS project. It is developed to fill the gap left by the dead CentOS stable release.
Rocky Linux 8 is a 1:1 binary compatible for of Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.
Download Links FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustMINIMAL INSTALLATION !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feren OS 2021.01 VM Images | Feren OS 2021.01 VirtualBox Image | Feren OS 2021.01 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ferenos-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ferenos-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Feren OS is an open-source Linux distribution based on the Ubuntu Linux operating system. It features KDE Plasma desktop.
Feren OS 2021.01 comes with Plasma 5.20, Linux Kernel 5.8, and many more updated packages.
READ: Release Notes
Download Links Feren OS 2021.01VirtualBox Image (Size 2.1GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.2GB)VM image comes pre-installed with Guest Additions / Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaro 21.0 VM Images | Manjaro 21.0 VirtualBox Image | Manjaro 21.0 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-21/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Manjaro is an open-source Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. It focuses on user friendliness and accessibility, and follows rolling release update model.
Manjaro 21.0 KDE comes with Linux Kernel 5.10 LTS, KDE 2.21, and Plasma 5.21.
READ: Release Notes
Download Links Manjaro 21.0 KDEFASTER DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 1.8GB)VMWare Image (Size 1.9GB)REGULAR DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parrot OS Security 4.10 VM Images | Parrot OS Security 4.10 VirtualBox Image | Parrot OS Security 4.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/parrotos-410/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/parrotos-410/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Parrot OS is an open-source Linux distribution based on Debian Linux. It is built with a focus on security, privacy, and development.
There are two editions of Parrot OS available to end-users, Parrot Home and Parrot Security.
Parrot Security edition provides penetration testing tools for attack mitigation, security research, forensics, and vulnerability assessment and is mainly used by penetration testers as an alternative to Kali Linux.
Parrot OS 4.10 comes with AnonSurf 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PureOS 9.0 VM Images | PureOS 9.0 VirtualBox Image | PureOS 9.0 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/pureos-90/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/pureos-90/</guid>
      <description>Introduction PureOS is an open-source Linux distribution based on Debian Linux. It is built with a focus on privacy and security.
PureOS 9.0 comes with GNOME (v3.30) as the desktop environment and a web browser called PureBrowser, a variant of Firefox focusing on privacy, Kernel v4.19, more updated packages.
Download Links PureOS 9.0VirtualBox Image (Size 1.6GB)VMWare Image (Size 1.6GB)VM images comes pre-installed with Guest Additions / VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artix Linux 20210101 VM Images | Artix Linux 2021 VirtualBox Image | Artix Linux 2021 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/artixlinux-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/artixlinux-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Artix Linux is an open-source Linux distribution based on Arch Linux. It follows rolling release model and uses OpenRC, runit or s6 init instead of systemd.
Artix Linux uses Pacman (package manager) to install, remove, and update software packages. Though Artix Linux has its own package repositories, it can use packages from Arch Linux repositories.
The image you are going to download contains Cinnamon desktop and OpenRC init system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux 2021.1 VM Images | Kali Linux 2021.1 VirtualBox Image | Kali Linux 2021.1 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kali Linux 2021.1 is the first Kali Linux release for the year 2021. It comes with Xfce 4.16, Terminals (mate-terminal, terminator and tilix terminals), Command Not Found, and few new tools such as Airgeddon, AltDNS, Arjun, etc.
You can read more about Kali Linux 2021.1 in release notes
You can also download pre-installed virtual images from the official site as well.
Download Links Kali Linux 2021.1VirtualBox Image (Size 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mageia 8 VM Images | Mageia 8 VirtualBox Image | Mageia 8 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mageia-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mageia-8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Mageia is a free and open-source Linux distribution. It was forked from Mandriva Linux and is a community project supported by the non-profit Mageia.Org organization of elected contributors.
Mageia has KDE Plasma Desktop, GNOME 3 and XFCE as its default user interfaces and offers a large repository of software, such as office and productivity applications and games.
READ: Release Notes
Download Links Mageia 8DOWNLOAD LINKS&amp;nbsp;CHECKSUM&amp;nbsp;DOWNLOAD LINKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EndeavourOS 2021 VM Images | EndeavourOS 2021 VirtualBox Image | EndeavourOS 2021 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endeavouros-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endeavouros-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction EndeavourOS 2021.02.03 is the latest release of EndeavourOS, an Arch Linux based Linux distribution. This latest release has combined offline and online installer.
The offline installer lets you install EndeavourOS with Xfce environment and the online option provides choice of environments from Xfce, Mate, Gnome, LXQt, Cinnamon, Plasma, Budgie, Deepin and Window Manager i3-WM.
Read: Features Of EndeavourOS 2021
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AlmaLinux 8 VM Images | AlmaLinux 8 VirtualBox Image | AlmaLinux 8 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/almalinux-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/almalinux-8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction AlmaLinux is an open-source RHEL fork built by the team of CloudLinux to fill the gap left by the dead CentOS stable release. AlmaLinux is a 1:1 binary compatible for of Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.
It is a completely free OS, backed by CloudLinux Inc, and with support until at least 2029.
Here, we provide ready to use AlmaLinux 8 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 20.04 VM Images | Xubuntu 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Xubuntu 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Xubuntu 20.04 (Focal Fossa) features the beautiful Xfce desktop environment. Xubuntu 20.04 was released April 23, 2020 and will be supported for three years, until April 29, 2023.
Xubuntu 20.04 comes with Xfce 4.14, Greybird theme 3.22.12, and community wallpapers and removed Python 2.
Read: New Features Of Xubuntu 20.04.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zorin OS 15.3 VM Images | Zorin OS 15.3 VirtualBox Image | Zorin OS 15.3 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/zorinos-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/zorinos-15/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Zorin OS is an open-source Linux distribution for computers. It follows the long-term releases of Ubuntu operating system and allows users to change the interface to resemble those of Microsoft Windows or MacOS.
Zorin offers Zorin OS 15.3 Ultimate, Zorin OS 15.3 Core, Zorin OS 15.3 Lite, and Zorin OS 15.3 Education editions.
Download Links Zorin OS 15.3 CoreFASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTED - Read Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q4OS 3.13 VM Images | Q4OS 3.13 VirtualBox Image | Q4OS 3.13 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/q4os-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/q4os-3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Q4OS is a free and open-source Linux distribution based on the Debian &amp;amp; Ubuntu operating system from Germany. It is a lightweight and user friendly distribution.
It comes with TDE (Trinity Desktop Environment) and KDE Plasma Desktop Environment.
Q4OS 3.13 receives Debian Buster 10.7 update, updated stable kernel, important security and bug fixes
Download Links Q4OS 3.13FASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTED - Read Why?VirtualBox Image (Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux 2021.01.01 VM Images | Arch Linux 2021 VirtualBox Image | Arch Linux 2021 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/archlinux-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/archlinux-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Arch Linux is an open-source Linux distribution that follows five principles: simplicity, modernity, pragmatism, user centrality, and versatility. it follows rolling release model which means there are no majaor releases and installation images are released every month.
Arch Linux uses Pacman (package manager) to install, remove, and update software packages.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepin 20.1 VM Images | Deepin 20.1 VirtualBox Image | Deepin 20.1 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-201/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Deepin is an open-source Linux distribution based on Debian&amp;rsquo;s stable branch. It features DDE, the Deepin Desktop Environment, built on Qt and available for various distributions like Manjaro, Arch or Fedora.
Deepin 20.1 comes with a new kernel 5.8 (stable), Debian 10.6 repositories, enhanced system stability and optimized performance. You can read more about the new release in the release notes.
Here, we provide ready to use Deepin 20.1 VirtualBox and VMware images for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garuda Linux 201205 VM Images | Garuda Linux 201205 VirtualBox Image | Garuda Linux 201205 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/garudalinux-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/garudalinux-2020/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Garuda Linux is a free and open-source rolling Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. It has KDE, GNOME, Xfce, Cinnamon, MATE, LXQt-kwin, Deepin, Wayfire, BSPWM and i3wm as its default user interfaces.
Download Links Garuda Linux 201205FASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTED - Read Why?VirtualBox Image (Size 2.5GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.7GB)REGULAR DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 2.5GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mageia 7.1 VM Images | Mageia 7.1 VirtualBox Image | Mageia 7.1 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mageia-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mageia-7/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Mageia is a free and open-source Linux distribution. It was forked from Mandriva Linux, and has KDE Plasma Desktop, GNOME 3 and XFCE as its default user interfaces.
Mageia offers a large repository of software, such as office and productivity applications and games.
Download Links Mageia 7.1FASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTED - Read Why?VirtualBox Image (Size 1.9GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.1GB)REGULAR DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaro 20.2 VM Images | Manjaro 20.2 VirtualBox Image | Manjaro 20.2 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-20/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Manjaro is a free and open-source Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. Manjaro has a focus on user friendliness and accessibility, and the system itself is designed to work fully &amp;ldquo;straight out of the box&amp;rdquo; with its variety of pre-installed software. It features a rolling release update model and uses Pacman as its package manager.
Manjaro comes with both a CLI and a graphical installer. The rolling release model means that the user does not need to upgrade/reinstall the whole system to keep it all up-to-date inline with the latest release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCLinuxOS 2020.10 VM Images | PCLinuxOS 2020.10 VirtualBox Image | PCLinuxOS 2020.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/pclinuxos-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/pclinuxos-2020/</guid>
      <description>Introduction PCLinuxOS is a free and open-source Linux distribution. It&amp;rsquo;s look and feel similar to Mandriva Linux, and has KDE Plasma Desktop, MATE and XFCE as its default user interfaces. It features a rolling release update model and uses apt-get as its package manager.
Download Links PCLinuxOS 2020.10FASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTED - Read Why?VirtualBox Image (Size 3.4GB)VMWare Image (Size 3.4GB)REGULAR DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux 2020.4 VM Images | Kali Linux 2020.4 VirtualBox Image | Kali Linux 2020.4 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kalilinux-2020/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kali Linux is a Linux distribution based on the Debian Linux operating system for advanced Penetration Testing and Security Auditing. It is developed, funded and maintained by Offensive Security.
Kali Linux contains more than 600 penetration testing tools. It follows rolling release model means that the user does not need to reinstall the whole system to keep it all up-to-date inline with the latest release.
You can also download VM images from the (official site)[https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArcoLinux 20.11 VM Images | ArcoLinux 20.11 VirtualBox Image | ArcoLinux 20.11 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/arcolinux-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/arcolinux-20/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ArcoLinux is Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. 90% of its packages are from Arch Linux. Elements of AUR repository are from GitHub, Debian, Red Hat, and compressed files. Themes, icons, tweaks, and configs are created by ArcoLinux.
ArcoLinux follows rolling release model means that the user does not need to reinstall the whole system to keep it all up-to-date inline with the latest release. Also, it releases ISOs on a bimonthly basis with the updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin 20.10 VM Images | Ubuntu Kylin 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Kylin 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntukylin-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntukylin-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Kylin 20.10 is the latest and an official derivative of Ubuntu 20.10 from Kirin Software Co., Ltd. It is a very friendly and easy to use desktop environment.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu Kylin 20.10.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links This image can be used on both VirtualBox and VMware Workstation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop!_OS 20.10 VM Images | Pop!_OS 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Pop!_OS 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pop!_OS 20.10 is the latest release from System76, Inc. Read more about Pop!_OS 20.10.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.Pop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin 20.04 VM Images | Ubuntu Kylin 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Kylin 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntukylin-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntukylin-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Kylin 20.04 is an official derivative of Ubuntu 20.04 from Kirin Software Co., Ltd. It is a very friendly and easy to use desktop environment.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu Kylin 20.04.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links This image can be used on both VirtualBox and VMware Workstation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Studio 22.04 VM Images | Ubuntu Studio 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Studio 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Studio 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish) is the latest Long Term Release and 31st release from Ubuntu Studio Project, supported for 3 years until April 2025.
Ubuntu Studio 22.04 made Dark Theme By Default, has support for rEFInd bootloader, Backports PPA and Plasma Backports.
This release will be the first LTS release of Ubuntu Studio that uses Plasma Desktop Environment.
Read: Release Notes
Download Links Ubuntu Studio 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Budgie 22.04 VM Images | Ubuntu Budgie 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Budgie 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntubudgie-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntubudgie-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Budgie 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish) is a LTS release from the Ubuntu Budgie Team, and it is an official community flavor of Ubuntu featuring the Budgie desktop. This release will be supported for 3 years, until April 2025.
This 22.04 release comes with Budgie Desktop v10.6 that has better application grouping, internal theme and panel refinements.
Budgie 22.04 comes with Linux Kernel v5.15, Firefox v93 using as snap, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 22.04 VM Images | Ubuntu 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish) is the latest Ubuntu release from Canonical. It was released on April 21st, 2022.
This release will be Ubuntu LTS (Long-term Supported) release and Extended Security Maintenance (ESM) 10 years. Ubuntu 22.04 will be 26th Ubuntu release since its inception.
RELEASE NOTES
Download Links Ubuntu 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish)FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustFASTER DOWNLOAD !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garuda Linux 2022 VM Images | Garuda Linux 2022 VirtualBox Image | Garuda Linux 2022 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/garudalinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/garudalinux/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Garuda Linux is a free and open-source rolling Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. It has KDE, GNOME, Xfce, Cinnamon, MATE, LXQt-kwin, Deepin, Wayfire, BSPWM and i3wm as its default user interfaces.
Read: FAQ - Garuda Linux
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Garuda Linux 2203DOWNLOAD LINKS&amp;nbsp;CHECKSUM&amp;nbsp;DOWNLOAD LINKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Mint Debian Edition 4 (LMDE 4) VM Images | Linux Mint Debian Edition 4 (LMDE 4) VirtualBox Image | Linux Mint Debian Edition 4 (LMDE 4) VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lmde-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lmde-4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction LMDE stands for “Linux Mint Debian Edition”, a Linux Mint project. It provides you the same user experience as Ubuntu but with Debian base packages.
LMDE comes with many improvements such as automated partitioning with LVM support, home directory encryption, automated installation of NVIDIA drivers, NVMe support, SecureBoot support, and much more.
We provide ready-to-use Linux Mint Debian Edition 4 (LMDE 4) VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slackware 15.0 VM Images | Slackware 15.0 VirtualBox Image | Slackware 15.0 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/slackware-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/slackware-15/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Slackware is an open-source Linux distribution created by Patrick Volkerding in 1993, and it is the oldest distribution that is still maintained.
Slackware follows design stability and simplicity as its principle, so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide graphical installation procedures, making it well suited for advanced and technically inclined Linux users.
Slackware 15 was officially released on 2nd Feb 2022 and is available for the IA-32 and x86_64 architectures and comes with kernel version 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 35 VM Images | Fedora 35 VirtualBox Image | Fedora 35 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-35/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fedora Workstation 35 was released on November 02, 2021, by the Fedora project, and it is an on-schedule release sixth in a row.
Fedora Workstation 35 comes with GNOME 41 that has been in development for six months of work by the GNOME project.GNOME 41 includes an improved software app, new multitasking settings, and better power management features. These changes make GNOME a smarter, more flexible, and richer interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xubuntu 21.10 VM Images | Xubuntu 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Xubuntu 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/xubuntu-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Xubuntu 21.10 (Impish Indri) is regular release of an official Ubuntu flavor that features Xfce desktop environment as the default desktop environment. it will be supported 9 months, until June 2022. If you need a stable environment, you can download Xubuntu 20.04 LTS instead.
Xubuntu comes with GNOME Disk Analyzer, GNOME Disk Utility, and Rhythmbox pre-installed. Pipewire is now included and can be used in conjuction with PulseAudio to improve playback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu 21.10 VM Images | Kubuntu 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Kubuntu 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubuntu 21.10 (Impish Indri) is a standard release that features the beautiful KDE Plasma 5.22.5. In addition, Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including a new 5.13-based kernel, KDE Frameworks 5.86, and KDE Gear 21.08.
It also includes Firefox 92 as the default browser, using the Debian package from the Ubuntu archive, LibreOffice 7.2.1, and Qt 5.15.2.
Kubuntu 21.10 will be supported for nine months until July 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lubuntu 21.10 VM Images | Lubuntu 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Lubuntu 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lubuntu 21.10 (Impish Indri) is standard release of an official Ubuntu flavor that features Lightweight Qt Desktop Environment (LXQt) as the default desktop environment. Lubuntu 21.10 will be supported 9 months until July 2022.
Lubuntu uses the Calamares installer in place of the Ubiquity installer that most other Ubuntu flavors use. Calamares 3.2.41.1 now included option of swapfile by default for full/erase disk installation.
Lubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including LXQt 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Budgie 21.10 VM Images | Ubuntu Budgie 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Budgie 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntubudgie-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntubudgie-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Budgie 21.10 (Impish Indri) is a regular release from the Ubuntu Budgie Team, and it is an official community flavor of Ubuntu featuring the Budgie desktop. This release will be supported for nine months until July 2022.
Ubuntu Budgie uses Budgie Desktop v10.5.3 in this release and has revamped dark theme with GTK+4 support. In addition, windows Shuffler now auto-moves and arranges windows and includes a Windows 11 like optional layout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Studio 21.10 VM Images | Ubuntu Studio 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Studio 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Studio 21.10 (Impish Indri) is the standard release from the Ubuntu Studio Project and will be supported for nine months until July 2022. Ubuntu Studio uses the same KDE Plasma desktop environment, Plasma v5.22, as Kubuntu 21.10 release.
Plasma 5.22 is now smooth while retaining familiar set up. Ubuntu Studio 21.10 ships the 5th scheduled bugfix release of KDE Plasma 5.22 (5.22.5).
It also comes with Linux Kernel v5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 21.10 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 03:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE 21.10 (Impish Indri) is the standard release from the Ubuntu MATE team and will be supported for nine months until July 2022. Ubuntu MATE team has put more effort into fixing bugs in MATE Desktop 1.26.0, optimizing performance, and plugging memory leaks. As a result, MATE Desktop is now faster and leaner.
It also comes with Linux Kernel 5.13, Firefox 96 as a snap package instead of a deb package, LibreOffice v7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 21.10 VM Images | Ubuntu 21.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 21.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2110/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu 21.10 is codenamed &amp;ldquo;Impish Indri&amp;rdquo; is an adjective that means &amp;ldquo;inclined to do slightly naughty things for fun&amp;rdquo;. It has been released on October 14th, 2021 by Canonical.
It is the final interim release before the next Ubuntu LTS release due to be released in April, 2022. This release will get support for 9 months with major bug fixes, critical security patches, and new app releases.
Ubuntu 21.10 is 25th Ubuntu release since its inception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Studio 20.04 VM Images | Ubuntu Studio 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu Studio 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntustudio-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu Studio 20.04 (Focal Fossa) is the latest Long Term Release from Ubuntu Studio Project, supported for 3 years until April 2023.
Ubuntu Studio 20.04 includes return of MyPaint 2.0, AVLDrums (as an LV2 plugin), Ubuntu Studio Contro, and Libreoffice.
This release will be the final release of Ubuntu Studio using the Xfce Desktop Environment.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu Studio 20.04 &amp;amp; Release Notes.
Download Links Ubuntu Studio 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu 21.04 VM Images | Kubuntu 21.04 VirtualBox Image | Kubuntu 21.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2104/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubuntu 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo) features the beautiful KDE Plasma 5.21 and KDE Applications 20.12.3. Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including a new 5.11-based kernel, Firefox 87, LibreOffice 7.1, and Qt 5.15.2.
Kubuntu 21.04 will be supported for 9 Months.
Read: New Features Of Kubuntu 21.04 &amp;amp; Release Notes
Download Links Kubuntu 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo)DOWNLOAD LINKS&amp;nbsp;CHECKSUM&amp;nbsp;DOWNLOAD LINKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lubuntu 21.04 VM Images | Lubuntu 21.04 VirtualBox Image | Lubuntu 21.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2104/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lubuntu 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo) is an official Ubuntu flavor features Lightweight Qt Desktop Environment (LXQt) as the default desktop environment. Lubuntu 21.04 will be supported until January 2022.
Lubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including LXQt 0.16.0 – with many improvements over 0.15 present in 20.10, Mozilla Firefox 87.0, LibreOffice 7.1.2 suite, VLC 3.0.12, Featherpad 0.17.1, Software Center 5.21.4, and much more.
Read: New Features Of Lubuntu 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 21.04 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 21.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 21.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2104/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo) is the standard release from Ubuntu MATE team, supported for 9 months until January 2022. It comes with latest MATE desktop 1.24.1, Firefox 87, LibreOffice 7.1.2.2, Evolution 3.40, and Celluloid 0.20.
Ubuntu MATE 21.04 includes Linux Kernel 5.11, better anonymous memory management, support for extended attributes in NFS, and much more.
Ubuntu MATE team is expected to release images for the Raspberry Pi in the days following the release for PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 21.04 VM Images | Ubuntu 21.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 21.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2104/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2104/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo) is an upcoming standard release from Canonical, supported for 9 months until January 2022.
Ubuntu 21.04 includes the 5.11 Linux kernel, better anonymous memory management, support for extended attributes in NFS, and much more.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu 21.04
Download Links Ubuntu 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo)FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustFASTER DOWNLOAD !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 34 VM Images | Fedora 34 VirtualBox Image | Fedora 34 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-34/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fedora project has announced Fedora Linux 34 beta&amp;rsquo;s availability on March 23, 2021, ahead of its stable release at the end of April.
After BTRFS became the default filesystem for Fedora Linux 33 desktop variants, Fedora Linux 34 enables transparent compression for more disk space.
Fedora 34 replaced PulseAudio with PipeWire to mix and manage audio streams. It also comes with GNOME 40, the newest release of the GNOME desktop environment, Kernel 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 20.10 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE 20.10 (Groovy Gorilla) is the latest standard release from Ubuntu MATE team, supported for 9 months until July 2021. It comes with latest MATE desktop 1.24.1, Firefox 81, LibreOffice 7.0.2, Evolution 3.38, and Celluloid 0.18.
Ubuntu MATE team is expected to release Ubuntu MATE 20.04 and 20.10 images for the Raspberry Pi in the coming days.
Ubuntu MATE 20.10 includes Linux Kernel 5.8, support for USB 4, XFS online repair and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lubuntu 20.10 VM Images | Lubuntu 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Lubuntu 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lubuntu 20.10 (Groovy Gorilla) is a latest official Ubuntu flavor features Lightweight Qt Desktop Environment (LXQt). Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including LXQt 0.15.0 – with many improvements over 0.14 present in 20.04, Mozilla Firefox 81.0.2, The LibreOffice 7.0.2 suite, VLC 3.0.11.1, Featherpad 0.12.1, Software Center 5.19.5, and much more.
Read: New Features Of Lubuntu 20.10.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu 20.10 VM Images | Kubuntu 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Kubuntu 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubuntu 20.10 (Groovy Gorilla) features the beautiful KDE Plasma 5.19.5 and KDE Applications 20.08. Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including a new 5.4-based kernel, LXD 4.6, MicroK8s 1.19, and digiKam 7.0.
Read: New Features Of Kubuntu 20.10.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links This image can be used on both VirtualBox and VMware Workstation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 33 VM Images | Fedora 33 VirtualBox Image | Fedora 33 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-33/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Fedora 33 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Fedora 33VirtualBox / VMware Image (Size 3.1GB)No Updates Installed
MD5 - 16d36a27ac35eccffb41db95ef4165ba
SHA-1 - 13f534db9a8d4e20b79500d3d42317fd2087c83cSystem Details &amp;amp; Password NOTESSYSTEM DETAILSLOGIN DETAILSvCPU: 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 20.10 VM Images | Ubuntu 20.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 20.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2010/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu 20.10 (Groovy Gorilla) is the latest standard release from Canonical, supported for 9 months. Ubuntu 20.10 is the first Ubuntu release to offer desktop images for the Raspberry Pi 4.
Ubuntu 20.10 includes Linux Kernel 5.8, support for USB 4, XFS online repair and much more.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu 20.10 &amp;amp; Release Notes
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android-x86 VM Images | Android-x86 VirtualBox Image | Android-x86 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/android-x86/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/android-x86/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Android-x86 is an open-source project that makes porting of Google&amp;rsquo;s Android mobile operating system to run on Intel x86 or AMD powered devices.
Chih-Wei Huang and Yi Sun originated the project in 2009 with series of patches to enable Android to run on tablets, netbooks, and PC&amp;rsquo;s.
just like other Linux distribution, the project releases pre-built ISO images which would run under live mode or installed to a hard disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux 2022 VM Images | Arch Linux 2022 VirtualBox Image | Arch Linux 2022 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/archlinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/archlinux/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Arch Linux is an open-source Linux distribution that follows five principles: simplicity, modernity, pragmatism, user centrality, and versatility.
Arch Linux uses Pacman, a package manager written specifically for Arch Linux. This is used to install, remove, and update software packages. It follows rolling release model which means there are no major releases and installation images are released every month.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lubuntu 18.04 VM Images | Lubuntu 18.04 VirtualBox Image | Lubuntu 18.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-1804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-1804/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lubuntu 18.04 is the Long Term Release release from Lubuntu Community. It is an official Ubuntu flavor that uses the Lightweight Qt Desktop Environment (LXQt) to provide a lightweight yet functional Linux distribution based on a rock-solid Ubuntu base.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lubuntu 20.04 VM Images | Lubuntu 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Lubuntu 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/lubuntu-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lubuntu 20.04 is the latest Long Term Release release from Lubuntu Community. It is an official Ubuntu flavor that uses the Lightweight Qt Desktop Environment (LXQt) to provide a lightweight yet functional Linux distribution based on a rock-solid Ubuntu base.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EndeavourOS 21.5 VM Images | EndeavourOS 21.5 VirtualBox Image | EndeavourOS 21.5 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endeavouros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endeavouros/</guid>
      <description>Introduction EndeavourOS is an Arch Linux based Linux distribution, the successor to Antergos, which was discontinued in 2019. It is a rolling release operating system.
Read: Features Of EndeavourOS Atlantis Neo 21.5
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links EndeavourOS Atlantis Neo 21.5DOWNLOAD LINKS&amp;nbsp;CHECKSUM&amp;nbsp;DOWNLOAD LINKS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Mint 20.3 VM Images | Linux Mint 20.3 VirtualBox Image | Linux Mint 20.3 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxmint-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxmint-20/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Linux Mint 20.3 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Linux Mint 20.3 FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustFASTER DOWNLOAD !!! AD SUPPORTEDVirtualBox Image (1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 32 VM Images | Fedora 32 VirtualBox Image | Fedora 32 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-32/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Fedora 32 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Fedora 32VirtualBox Image (Size 4.5GB)VMware Image - Part 1 (Size 4.7GB)VMware Image - Part 2 (Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 22.04 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE is an open-source Linux distribution and an official derivative of Ubuntu. It uses MATE desktop environment as its graphical interface.
Ubuntu MATE 22.04 is the latest Long Term Release featuring MATE 1.26.1, based on Ubuntu 22.04 LTS (Jammy Jellyfish). This LTS release will be supported till April 2025.
Ubuntu MATE 22.04 comes with Linux 5.15, Firefox 99.0, Celluloid 0.20, Evolution 3.44 &amp;amp; LibreOffice 7.3.2.1.
Read: Release Notes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu 22.04 VM Images | Kubuntu 22.04 VirtualBox Image | Kubuntu 22.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2204/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubuntu 22.04 (Jammy Jellyfish) features the beautiful Plasma 5.24 LTS : simple by default, powerful when needed. Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including a new 5.15-based kernel, KDE Frameworks 5.92, and KDE Gear (formerly Applications) 21.12.3.
Firefox 99 is the default browser, using a snap from the Ubuntu archive.
LibreOffice 7.3.2.2 is provided by default in the full installation.
Kubuntu 22.04 ships with Qt 5.15.3
Read: New Features Of Kubuntu 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>antiX 21 VM Images | antiX 21 VirtualBox Image | antiX 21 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/antix-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/antix-21/</guid>
      <description>Introduction antiX 21 (Grup Yorum) is a Linux distribution based on Debian 11 (Bullseye) with sysVinit or runit system. It is comparatively lightweight and suitable for older computers, available for both 32 and 64-bit architecture.
64-bit version of antiX Linux comes with2 kernels. Legacy 4.9 and Modern 5.10. While the default kernel will be the Modern 5.10.
You can get updates and additional packages using the apt-get from Debian-compatible repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 18.04.5 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 18.04.5 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 18.04.5 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-1804/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-1804/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE 18.04.5 is the previous Long Term Release featuring MATE Desktop 1.20.1, based on Ubuntu 18.04.5 LTS (Bionic Beaver). This LTS release will be supported till April 2021.
Read: Release Notes
Download Links Ubuntu MATE 18.04.5 (Bionic Beaver)FASTER DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 2.6GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.9GB)REGULAR DOWNLOADVirtualBox Image (Size 2.6GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.9GB)VM image comes pre-installed with Guest Additions/Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solus 4.2 VM Images | Solus 4.2 VirtualBox Image | Solus 4.2 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/solus-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/solus-42/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Solus 4.2 is the latest release of Solus 4 “Fortitude”. This release features Firefox 85.0, LibreOffice 7.0.4.2, Thunderbird 78.6.1, and Linux kernel 5.10.12.
Solus offers Budgie, GNOME, and MATE editions. Here, I provide you Budgie edition virtual machine with Budgie v10.5.2.
Solus 4.2 supports many new features and hardware capabilities.
READ: Release Notes
Download Links Solus 4.2 (Budgie)VirtualBox Image (Size 2.6GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu MATE 20.04.2 VM Images | Ubuntu MATE 20.04.2 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu MATE 20.04.2 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntumate-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu MATE is a open-source Linux distribution and an official derivative of Ubuntu. It uses MATE desktop environment as its default user interface.
Ubuntu MATE 20.04.2 is the latest Long Term Release featuring MATE 1.24, based on Ubuntu 20.04.2 LTS (Focal Fossa). This LTS release will be supported till April 2023.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu MATE 20.04 &amp;amp; Release Notes
Download Links Ubuntu MATE 20.04.2 (Focal Fossa)FASTER DOWNLOAD AD SUPPORTEDVirtualBox Image (Size 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openSUSE 15.3 VM Images | openSUSE 15.3 VirtualBox Image | openSUSE 15.3 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/opensuse-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/opensuse-15/</guid>
      <description>Introduction openSUSE Leap 15.3 is the latest Leap minor release from The openSUSE Project. It was released on December 3, 2021, and comes with a maintenance lifecycle of 11 months i.e., November 2022.
Read: Features Of openSUSE Leap 15.3 &amp;amp; Release Notes
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links openSUSE Leap 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop!_OS 20.04 VM Images | Pop!_OS 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Pop!_OS 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/popos-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pop!_OS 20.04 is the latest release from System76, Inc. Read more about Pop!_OS 20.04.
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.Pop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu 20.04 VM Images | Kubuntu 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Kubuntu 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kubuntu-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubuntu 20.04 (Focal Fossa) features the beautiful KDE Plasma 5.18 LTS: simple by default, powerful when needed. Kubuntu comes with updates to many core packages, including a new 5.4-based kernel, KDE Frameworks 5.68, Plasma 5.18 LTS and KDE Applications 19.12.3.
Read: New Features Of Kubuntu 20.04.
Download Links Kubuntu 20.04 LTS (Focal Fossa)VirtualBox Image (Size 3GB)VMWare Image (Size 3.1GB)VM images comes pre-installed with VirtualBox Guest Additions / Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>antiX 19 VM Images | antiX 19 VirtualBox Image | antiX 19 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/antix-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/antix-19/</guid>
      <description>Introduction antiX is a Linux distribution built directly on Debian Stable. It is comparatively lightweight and suitable for older computers, while also providing cutting edge kernel and applications, as well as updates and additions via the apt-get package system and Debian-compatible repositories.
Here, we provide ready to use antiX 19 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDE neon VM Images | KDE neon VirtualBox Image | KDE neon VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kdeneon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kdeneon/</guid>
      <description>Introduction KDE neon is a Linux distribution developed by KDE based on the most recent Ubuntu long-term support (LTS) release, bundled with a set of additional software repositories containing the latest 64-bit versions of the Plasma 5 desktop environment/framework, Qt 5 toolkit and other compatible KDE software.
First announced in June 2016 by Kubuntu founder Jonathan Riddell following his departure from Canonical (Ubuntu&amp;rsquo;s parent company), it has been adopted by a steadily growing number of Linux users, regularly appearing in the Top 20 on DistroWatch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepin 15.11 VM Images | Deepin 15.11 VirtualBox Image | Deepin 15.11 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-1511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/deepin-1511/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Deepin (stylized as deepin; formerly known as Linux Deepin and Hiweed Linux) is a Linux distribution based on Debian&amp;rsquo;s stable branch. It features DDE, the Deepin Desktop Environment, built on Qt and available for various distributions like Manjaro, Arch or Fedora. As of version 15.10 it also uses dde-kwin, a set of patches for KDE Plasma&amp;rsquo;s window manager. In 2019, Huawei started to ship Linux laptops pre-installed with deepin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solus 4.1 VM Images | Solus 4.1 VirtualBox Image | Solus 4.1 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/solus-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/solus-41/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Solus is an independently developed desktop operating system based on the Linux kernel and using its own desktop environment derived from GNOME. Starting with the Debian branch of Linux it migrated to a unique approach including Pisi and Evolve OS. It is offered as a curated rolling release model under the slogan &amp;ldquo;Install Today. Updates Forever&amp;rdquo;.
Solus contains a wide variety of desktop environments depending on release chosen, options include Solus&#39; own Budgie Desktop, GNOME, MATE and KDE Plasma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 20.04 VM Images | Ubuntu 20.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 20.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-2004/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ubuntu 20.04 (Focal Fossa) is the latest Long Term Release from Canonical.
Read: New Features Of Ubuntu 20.04 &amp;amp; Release Notes
The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MX Linux 21 VM Images | MX Linux 21 VirtualBox Image | MX Linux 21 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mxlinux-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mxlinux-21/</guid>
      <description>Introduction MX Linux 21 &amp;ldquo;Wildflower&amp;rdquo; is a midweight Linux operating system based on Debian 11 &amp;ldquo;Bullseye&amp;rdquo;, released by antiX and the MX communities. It was released on October 21, 2021.
MX Linux 21 comes with Kernel 5.10 and is available as Xfce (i386 and x64), KDE (x64), or Fluxbox (i386 and x64) versions. Xfce version includes Xfce 4.16, Plasma version includes Plasma desktop 5.20, and Fluxbox version includes fluxbox 1.3.7 with mx-fluxbox 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Lite 5.4 VirtualBox Image | Linux Lite 5.4 VMware Image | Linux Lite 5.4 VM Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxlite-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxlite-54/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Linux Lite is a lightweight operating system based on Ubuntu and Debian. It was created to provide a more user-friendly experience for computers with low resources, but it&amp;rsquo;s also great for older machines that are still in use. With Linux Lite OS, you can enjoy the same benefits as Ubuntu without any of the hassles.
Thanks to Xfce desktop. Linux Lite OS has a lot of customizable options regarding how you can customize your desktop, including wallpapers (or backgrounds), themes, and icons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bodhi Linux 6.0.0 VirtualBox Image | Bodhi Linux 6.0.0 VMware Image | Bodhi Linux 6.0.0 VM Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/bodhilinux-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/bodhilinux-6/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bodhi Linux is a light-weight, Ubuntu-based distribution with an elegant and simplistic design. It is also one of the few independent distributions that do not use GNOME or KDE as its default desktop environment.
The project was founded by Jeff Hoogland (aka &amp;ldquo;JeffHo&amp;rdquo;) back in 2008, but it was not until 2011 when the first stable release came out that Bodhi really started to get some traction.
It has all the makings for a great light-weight Linux distribution: it boots really quickly, loads web pages in the blink of an eye, and has a snappy, well-designed interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>elementary OS 6 VirtualBox Image | elementary OS 6 VMware Image | elementary OS 6 VM Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/elementary-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/elementary-6/</guid>
      <description>Introduction elementary OS is a Linux-based operating system that runs on computers and laptops. It has been around since 2011, and it is open-source.
elementary OS uses the Pantheon desktop environment to provide users with an aesthetically pleasing user interface. It is designed to look similar to Mac OS X, with features like icons in the dock at the bottom of the screen.
elementary OS 6 Odin is the latest release from Elementary Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>elementary OS 5.1 VirtualBox Image | elementary OS 5.1 VMware Image | elementary OS 5.1 VM Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/elementary-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/elementary-51/</guid>
      <description>Introduction elementary OS is a Linux distribution based on Ubuntu that focuses mainly on non-technical users. It promotes itself as a “fast, open, and privacy-respecting” replacement to macOS and Windows and has a pay-what-you-want model.The operating system, the desktop environment (called Pantheon), and accompanying applications are developed and maintained by elementary, Inc.
Download Links elementary OS 5.1VirtualBox / VMware Image (Size 3.0 GB)VM image comes pre-installed with Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaro 19 VM Images | Manjaro 19 VirtualBox Image | Manjaro 19 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/manjaro-19/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Manjaro is a free and open-source Linux distribution based on the Arch Linux operating system. Manjaro has a focus on user friendliness and accessibility, and the system itself is designed to work fully &amp;ldquo;straight out of the box&amp;rdquo; with its variety of pre-installed software. It features a rolling release update model and uses Pacman as its package manager.
Manjaro comes with both a CLI and a graphical installer. The rolling release model means that the user does not need to upgrade/reinstall the whole system to keep it all up-to-date inline with the latest release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MX Linux 19.3 VM Images | MX Linux 19.3 VirtualBox Image | MX Linux 19.3 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mxlinux-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/mxlinux-19/</guid>
      <description>Introduction MX Linux is a midweight Linux operating system based on Debian stable and using core antiX components, with additional software created or packaged by the MX community. It is developed as a cooperative venture between the antiX and former MEPIS communities, aiming to use the best tools and talents from each of these distributions.
The community&amp;rsquo;s stated goal is to &amp;ldquo;combine an elegant and efficient desktop with simple configuration, high stability, solid performance and medium-sized footprint&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CentOS Stream 9 VM Images | CentOS Stream 9 VirtualBox Image | CentOS Stream 9 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centosstream-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centosstream-9/</guid>
      <description>Introduction CentOS Stream 9 is a free and open-source enterprise-class Linux distribution. It is a midstream between the upstream Fedora Linux and the downstream development for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 (RHEL) with additional supports from the CentOS community.
Each major release of CentOS stream starts from a stable release of Fedora Linux. CentOS Stream 9 begins with Fedora 34 and continue further.
There are many reasons to use CentOS Stream 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CentOS Stream 8 VM Images | CentOS Stream 8 VirtualBox Image | CentOS Stream 8 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centosstream-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centosstream-8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction CentOS Stream 8 is a free and open-source enterprise-class Linux distribution. It is a midstream between the upstream development in Fedora Linux and the downstream development for Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) with additional supports from the CentOS community.
There are many reasons to use CentOS Stream 8. One is that it is a rolling release distribution. You do not have to wait for an entire upgrade cycle to experience new features in the rolling release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CentOS 8 VM Images | CentOS 8 VirtualBox Image | CentOS 8 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use CentOS 8 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa. However, sometime you may face network issues due to interface naming, especially in Red Hat Enterprise Linux derivatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CentOS 7 VM Images | CentOS 7 VirtualBox Image | CentOS 7 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-7/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use CentOS 7 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa. However, sometime you may face network issues due to interface naming, especially in Red Hat Enterprise Linux derivatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peppermint 10 VM Images | Peppermint 10 VirtualBox Image | Peppermint 10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/peppermint-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/peppermint-10/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Peppermint OS is an open-source Linux distribution based on Lubuntu, which itself is a derivative of the Ubuntu operating system.
It uses LXDE desktop environment and provides environment for newcomers and requires relatively low hardware resources to run.
This version, Peppermint 10 is based on Ubuntu 18.04 LTS.
Download Links Peppermint 10VirtualBox Image (Size 2.1GB)VMWare Image (Size 2.2GB)VM images comes pre-installed with VirtualBox Guest Additions / Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 18.04 VM Images | Ubuntu 18.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 18.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1804/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1804/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Ubuntu 18.04 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Ubuntu 18.04.6 FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustFASTER DOWNLOAD !!! AD SUPPORTEDVirtualBox Image (2.8 GB)VMware Image (2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 16.04 VM Images | Ubuntu 16.04 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 16.04 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1604/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1604/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Ubuntu 16.04 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.Ubuntu 16.04.07 LTS Ubuntu 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian 11 VM Images | Debian 11 VirtualBox Image | Debian 11 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-11/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Debian project has released a new version of the it&amp;rsquo;s Linux-based operating system, Debian 11 (code name Bullseye) on August 14th, 2021. Debian 11 has been released after two years of development.
This release includes over 11 thousands new packages which takes the total count of packages to 59 thousands. It supports mounting exFAT files without installing additional packages.
Read: Release Notes Of Debian 11
Here, we provide ready to use Debian 11 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian 10 VM Images | Debian 10 VirtualBox Image | Debian 10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 18:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-10/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Debian 10 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Debian 10.11.0 FASTER DOWNLOADOwn ServerREGULAR DOWNLOADSourceForgeCHECKSUMMustMINIMAL INSTALLATION !!! AD SUPPORTEDVirtualBox Image (380 MB)VMware Image (380 MB)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;REGULAR INSTALLATION - GNOME DESKTOP !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KaOS 2021.01 VM Images | KaOS 2021.01 VirtualBox Image | KaOS 2021.01 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kaos-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/kaos-2021/</guid>
      <description>Introduction KaOS is an open-source Linux distribution that is built from scratch. It follows rolling-release development model and built with latest KDE desktop environment for x86_64 architecture.
KaOS 2021.01 comes with Plasma 5 as the default desktop,KDE Applications 20.12.1, Linux kernel 5.10.6, Nvidia drivers, and many more updated packages.
READ: Release Notes
Here, we provide ready to use KaOS 2021.01 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.
Download Links KaOS 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeckoLinux 152.210223 VM Images | GeckoLinux 152.210223 VirtualBox Image | GeckoLinux 152.210223 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/geckolinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/geckolinux/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Devuan is an open-source Linux distribution based on openSUSE. It is available in two editions: Static, which is based on openSUSE Leap, and Rolling, which is based on openSUSE Tumbleweed.
Here, the given images are Static editions. GeckoLinux 152.210223 is based on openSUSE Leap 15.2. It comes with MATE 1.24, Linux kernel 5.3.18, and many more updated packages.
READ: Release Notes
Here, we provide ready to use GeckoLinux 152.210223 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless OS 3.9.0 VM Images | Endless OS 3.9.0 VirtualBox Image | Endless OS 3.9.0 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endlessos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 09:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/endlessos/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Endless is an open-source Linux distribution, a derivative of Debian operating system. It uses a read-only root filesystem managed by OSTree and Flatpak for application management and update.
Endless OS 3.9.0 comes with GNOME 3.38, Linux kernel 5.8, Nvidia driver 450.66, and many more updated packages.
READ: Release Notes
Here, we provide ready to use Endless OS 3.9.0 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.
Download Links Endless OS 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devuan 3.1.0 VM Images | Devuan 3.1.0 VirtualBox Image | Devuan 3.1.0 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/devuan-310/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 09:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/devuan-310/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Devuan is an open-source Linux distribution, a fork of Debian operating system. It uses sysvinit, runit or OpenRC instead of systemd as init systems.
Devuan 3.1.0 comes with Linux kernel 4.19, Firefox ESR 78, lightdm 1.26, and many more updated packages.
READ: Release Notes
Here, we provide ready to use Devuan 3.1.0 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements.
Download Links Devuan 3.1.0VirtualBox Image (Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian 9 VM Images | Debian 9 VirtualBox Image | Debian 9 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 09:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/debian-9/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Debian 9 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa.Debian 9.13.0 Debian 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CentOS 6 VM Images | CentOS 6 VirtualBox Image | CentOS 6 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/centos-6/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use CentOS 6 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Both VirtualBox and VMware support OVA &amp; OVF image formats which means you can use VirtualBox image on VMware and vice versa. However, sometime you may face network issues due to interface naming, especially in Red Hat Enterprise Linux derivatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 19.10 VM Images | Ubuntu 19.10 VirtualBox Image | Ubuntu 19.10 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1910/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/ubuntu-1910/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Ubuntu 19.10 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links This image can be used on both VirtualBox and VMware Workstation.Ubuntu 19.10VirtualBox / VMware Image (Size 4GB)VM image comes pre-installed with Open VM Tools for better performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 31 VM Images | Fedora 31 VirtualBox Image | Fedora 31 VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/fedora-31/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Fedora 31 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links Fedora 31VirtualBox Image - Part 1 (Size 4.1GB)VirtualBox Image - Part 2 (Size 3.3GB)VMware Image - Part 1 (Size 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Mint 19.x VM Images | Linux Mint 19.x VirtualBox Image | Linux Mint 19.x VMware Image</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxmint-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/linuxmint-19/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here, we provide ready to use Linux Mint 19 VirtualBox and VMware images for urgent requirements. The VirtualBox and VMware images are created in such a way that they are less in size but contains all the standard packages required for instant run.
Download Links This image can be used on both VirtualBox and VMware Workstation.Linux Mint 19.3VirtualBox / VMware Image (Size 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Linux VirtualBox Images | Linux VirtualBox Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/virtualbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/virtualbox/</guid>
      <description>List of VirtualBox Images 
 M = Minimal Installation / G = Graphical Installation  Image NameDownload LinkCentOS Stream 9Download (M - 0.7 GB / G - 1.7 GB)CentOS Stream 8Download (M - 0.6 GB / G - 1.6 GB)CentOS 8.4.2105Download (M - 0.6 GB / G - 1.6 GB)CentOS 7.9.2009Download (M - 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Linux VMware Images | Linux VMware Images</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/vmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 10:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/vmware/</guid>
      <description>List of VMware Images 
 M = Minimal Installation / G = Graphical Installation  Image NameDownload LinkCentOS Stream 9Download (M - 0.7 GB / G - 1.6 GB)CentOS Stream 8Download (M - 0.6 GB / G - 1.6 GB)CentOS 8.4.2105Download (M - 0.6 GB / G - 1.7 GB)CentOS 7.9.2009Download (M - 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
