<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Linux VM Images - Download VirtualBox and VMware Images</title>
    <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Linux VM Images - Download VirtualBox and VMware Images</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 02:59:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy - In A Fair Way  </title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This privacy policy has been compiled to serve better those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate Now - For a better delivery</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate Now 

I (Yes!) thank you for visting our website and I hope you have found what you are looking for. I started this site keeping one thing in my mind that why not provide faster way to download VM images for people who wants to do the things super fast. To provide a faster site for you, I don&#39;t display advertisements in this site. To continue to serve you well, please support me with just $1 by becoming a Patron</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us - In A Better Way  </title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us 
 If you found any issues using VM images, please do reach us at clicking here or mail us at linuxvmimages@gmail.com with the link to the page and a detailed description of the issue.
Provide us at least 3-5 days to respond to your report and we are more than happy to assitst you.
Thank you for your understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DMCA - Report Copyright Infringement </title>
      <link>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/dmca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 02:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.linuxvmimages.com/pages/dmca/</guid>
      <description>Report Copyright Infringement 
 VirtualBox and VMware logos are registered trademark of respective owners. We hold no rights for operating systems. VM images shared here are for learning purposes.
If you found any VM images / material that violates your copyright, please do reach us at clicking here or mail us at linuxvmimages@gmail.com with the link to the page and a detailed description of the infringement.
Provide us at least 3-5 days to respond to your report and we are more than happy to remove your material from our site if we found it violates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
